Sometimes your family, friends, or community can help.
They can help you solve problems,
which can lower some of the triggers.
Your family might also try to talk more
about good things that happened.
This helps you enjoy those happy times more.
Finally, you might start planning a fun event,
and we'll try this later too.
Just like events affect kids in different ways,
these ways to help also work differently for each kid.
For some kids, exercise helps,
but writing in a journal does not.
For some, talking to friends helps,
but for others, it has to be a family member.
And some kids can get help from a mental health professional.
This can be a school counselor or someone else in their community.
These helpers have many names
at counselors, social workers, or psychologists.
Today, we will just call them counselors.